{
    "id": "a17113fb1ab54843b15d794deb320d71",
    "title": "Comparatives worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "82a5ec83094f4c708103264321d3d4d0",
            "title": "Comparatives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Mount Everest is ……………… than Mount K",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "high",
                        "more high",
                        "higher"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The sun is ....................... than the moon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more hot",
                        "hotter",
                        "hottest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The moon is not as ..................... . as the sun.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hot",
                        "hotter",
                        "hottest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Iron is …..................... . wood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more heavy than",
                        "heavier than",
                        "heaviest than"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wood is not as ......................... as iron.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "heavy",
                        "heavier",
                        "heaviest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Dogs are ........................... than cats.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "faithful",
                        "more faithful",
                        "most faithful"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cats are ....................... than dogs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "low faithful",
                        "less faithful",
                        "lesser faithful"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The sparrow is ....................... than the crow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "small",
                        "smaller",
                        "smallest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The crow is not as ....................... as the sparrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "small",
                        "smaller",
                        "smallest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The elephant is the ...................... of the land animals.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bigger",
                        "biggest",
                        "more big"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Samuel is ............................ any other boy in the class",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "the smartest",
                        "smarter than",
                        "the smarter than"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}